Spy War about Top Secret
Finished, Finished
That's our teacher's vase.
What to do, What to
do? What to do?
I'll apologize
You will be condemned an punished for
standing until this afternoon
At the end the teacher will forget it
While you are punished for standing
he's gone home
Suneo, What shall I do?
I don't know
I'd better say nothing
but the condition is...
Don't be lazy while on duty
That's right, we are all working
Yes
Sorry
We'll do the rest
You can go home
You don't like cleaning
I will do them all
if others don't like that
Suneo is really a good person
right
Simply like god
respectable
Right
Can you please make it cleaner?
Very angry
Very angry, this damned Suneo
How come so slow?
l am waiting for you
Go and buy some meat
on the market, hurry
Why do I have to go?
About the vase
You want me find the ball in water?
This is too much.
Vase
What do you mean with vase?
This is like incantation
when cursing
Nobita will follow you everything
whenever you say "vase"to him
Finally found it
Nobita, give us some change money
Why do you want it from me?
vase
Help. Help
Our yard has to be cleaned up
Such a group of bad people
I ...What should I do?
You can count on me
I won't let you come short
Doraemon
Wonderful, Doraemon
You are my only reliable one
Nothing I can not achieve
First go to school
Re-light it
So your weakness will disappear
Wonderful
Now you can go to sleep
without any concern any more
Nobita, is there
anything else to do?
Oh, yes, I forgot cleaning
Suneo's yard
You junk good man
Are you not angry
if others treat you this way?
When you say that
I am getting more angry
This damned guy, Suneo.
Revenge on him
How to revenge?
What's this?
SPY eye ball
As soon as it turns
It goes to monitor Suneo
and find his weakness
Everything will appear on the TV
what that eye ball sees
Suneo's family in on TV
Today, I am alone make the
whole classroom clean
Suneo is really a good boy
Then I go reading books
Nonsense
Sitting in front of the mirror for long
What does he want to do?
You'll never fed up
by watching your own face
The word "beauty"
is for me there.
Can't hear that, too extreme
Too funny, I will tell everybody
No more, my stomach gets
pain by laughing
Oh my god, we have to do homework
Oh yes, we'll let Nobita
do that this evening
No, I won't help you do so
I'll let you know the result immediately
Well, fall asleep?
If got even thorough weakness
that will be more helpful...
What can we see on his face?
Looking forward to seeing that
Why do you do so again?
What?
What is he doing?
Suneo, I told you many times
Don't forget change
diaper before go to sleep.
Okay
ls this thorough?
This time Suneo
can walk out the gate.
I am so angry
Nobita will get that anger
Nobita, come to my home at once
You come to my home at once
You forget?
Vase, vase
Vase?
I don't understand what you are talking
What?
Get the evidence, evidence.
Really
Oh?
Vase
I see it. I see it.
No, Nobita broke it
The word “beauty“
Have the diaper on
I beg you, not to tell anybody
Then you help me do homework
Diaper
Vase
This is like so
What should you do further?
Really, if you say "vase"
to Nobita
He will do so for sure
Really, are you joking?
The let's try.
Nobita
You stand upside down without
cloths an then shout "wo, wo"
Why do I have to do so?
Vase
Wo, wo
Lucky gun
Come, come
Painful
Painful, really
who did that, very angry
That's too much. Actually we
wanted to play in your home.
If so, then forget about it.
Is that Shizuka?
No, hi, hi
Dumped
For Shizuka
didn't eat the cake yesterday
Stayed extra here
no other choice
So I had to eat it on my own
How painful, why come again and again?
So sorry
That's my cake
Guest is here
wait a moment
How can you do that?
What a bad luck, come and read books
Well, where are the
caricature books over there?
Dad took them away
He said to read them in bus
My god
People really have days
with lots of bad lucks
Indeed true
ls there any good way
to get the luck better?
Nothing as I know
What's that?
Hand gun
Hand gun with serial shots
Bullets are red and black
First so, then so.
If shot by red bullet, you'll
have good luck whole day long
Really?
If shot by black bullet,you'll
never meet anything good whole day long
How come?
Doraemon, take away black bullet
That doesn't work.
If bullets are not input
together,they won't work.
Besides, you can't get
any good luck without risk.
That's too selfish
Red bullets are more
than black ones.
Times more
Well, let's have a try.
What's wrong? Pull the trigger.
No choice, too terrible
Useless
Well, we need to find
somebody have a try
Doraemon
No joke
See you later.
Mom
What?
Pull the trigger like this
If it's red bullet, then it's good luck.
But if it's black bullet, your luck
on that day won't be good
It seems interesting
I particular let mom
shot the first bullet.
Reakkt? It's
a bit terrible.
It does not matter.
Mom is usually very
careful with everything
Let me have a try
So...
Suddenly, I feel very well.
It seems to be red one
Oh, god, one less
Ms. Nobita
I forgot very important thing.
I bought some gift
when traveled abroad.
Thank you
Look
What to do, What to do
OK, it's my turn
Oh, no.
I always feel it's a black bullet.
So it is.
Men have to have charm.
Charm
Right, right
I got a good method.
That's right.
I did not say
Before black bullet appears
use that on others
Then you can shoot straightly.
Is there anything like that?
Let me play, let me play.
I love this kind of game the most.
I have to say first.
Some remaining bullets
are black bullet with bad luck.
Are you afraid of this game?
From the possibility
they are black bullets for sure.
It's red
Bullet
Feeling very good
very happy
Gian, sometimes
bring you for movie
Seldom to get
Dady, let's go...
See you later.
Oh, I got the circle
Admirable
I should have shot
It's too late to say so
ls there any shot?
Try it bravely
NO, this time it's black bullet for sure
Impossible
red bullets in sequence
Suneo, you talk too much
Do you want to try your luck?
If it's red bullet, then good luck
But the remaining black bullet
bring bad luck.
If it's so
What's the matter
everybody is timid.
How about yourself
You too, you too.
It's count on me
I am coming
Suneo, can you make it?
I am pulling the trigger.
It's black, black bullet.
It's red bullet
Suneo is actually so brave.
I am sorry. Let's go
and play together.
It was your false
Look, only black bullet left
It's not a petty not to have the stuff
You can't through it away
It's hand gun, hand gun
I want to shoot
Don't point it at me
Stop it
Don't run away. I'll shoot
Hide yourself
That kind thinks
we are playing with him
What a bad luck, damned.
Found it
I want to shoot
Stop it
Don't
This brings me
bad luck all the time
It's you, always abuse him
No... no...
What are you doing
All in thousand
All savings in the whole year is gone
Too panic
will bring back luck
Be careful going home
If I thought of that...
Oh, my god
What kind of bad result will be?
Be careful
Oh, my god
Take today as a day
of bad luck, forget it
Get away! As if it had
nothing to do with you.
Cursing camera
Doraemon
I can't take it, can't take it.
It come back again.
I know that even if you don't say
Suneo abused you again
Bad guy
Today I will definitely
let you know something hard
NO need to say
you can understand me
This is brave Doraemon
Unforgettable
Nobita abusing me
Also means abusing me
I have hidden powerful
weapon, never used before
The so called devil is this
Cursing camera
If using this one...
Just imagining is terrible enough...
I'll take you in
NO choice, I can't do that
Even the worst people
this is too brutal
I really can't make it.
It's wild Doraemon.
What do you mean wild?
Your face looks funny
Regardless laughing or not
YOU bloody guy, I won't let you go
What are you doing?
Taking pictures for me?
I still can't make it
Strange Doraemon
Doraemon
Look quite casual
Doraemon has a camera in hand
Take a sleeping picture
Feeling as if electro-shock
Am I too sensitive?
This camera is very interesting.
Even closer
What are you talking about?
Was that a thunder?
Camera making human idol?
Right
This is for your last birthday
Human idol
Thanks
What? You took a picture
of mine with that camera?
Yes, just did that.
Cursing camera?
What incantation?
I let you see the evidence
Somebody comes here occasionally
I know that
The problem lies on human idol.
You see it clearly.
Stick your arm with needle
Oh, painful
Next is chest
Chest pain, painful
Hit your head
Painful
Stop, stop
painful...
So you understand
Whatever you do against human
idol, it will reflect to people
If somebody tears
my human idol apart...
Then I will be torn apart, too
Human idol?
I gave those human idols to Yasuko
She said to play with
human idols somewhere
She is rough
maybe has damaged it
Damned
We have to find her right now
No here
Where did she go?
Painful
Thrown on the ground
What a strange human idol!
Let's play doctor doll.
Okay, okay
Really bad, fever to how much?
Let here cool down.
Also let him cool down?
Put it in the refrigerator.
Suddenly felt very cold
What's wrong with you? Got a cold?
It's boring only with fever.
Then let's play worse sickness.
So cold
How come?
Very itchy
Stop it
Head, chest, stomach, hand
and feet are all sick.
So much sickness?
Itchy, itchy
very itchy...
It seems impossible without operation.
Operation, operation.
Painful, painful
It's not easy to cut
Hit it with a hammer
Doraemon
Too late for operation, dead.
Dead, dead
Finally you stopped
How petty, dead
Oh, my god
Its' Doraemon's human idol.
Yes, dead
Really?
Let me see
Get him a quite formal morning
First burn it, then berry it in earth
very hot...
very hot, very hot...
Oh, my god.
What?
Really fall from heaven
You are not allowed
to touch that human idol
Seemingly whatever you
do against this human idol
Doraemon has the
same reaction
So it is, kick that
painful
So is it
Like this
Stop it
Finally saved back
Those two remaining human
idols have to be taken back.
Thank goodness
Finally it becomes mild.
He treated me like that
I took that in pictures
Punish him, punish him
It's so cold, how come.
Oh god, How could that happen?
Build up subway
I have to wait for
long even come out with mom
Oh god, hurry.
Hurry to home
Dady is coming back
Oh, yes, dady's company
is right in the near, pick him up
We still need to go
Its' hard to be follower
It's right here
It's daddy.
It shocked me
How about everyone?
We go to department store shopping.
So it is
then go home together
So many people
Now it's rush hour
Don't get lost.
These people will take the same bus.
Don't forget anything when getting off.
Daddy took that bus
yesterday for work.
How hard.
Got used to that.
I can't move.
It's too pitiful
Really want to think an idea for daddy.
I have one
I have one good idea.
Good, wonderful... congratulations
What good idea?
Give him a present on daddy's birthday.
This is really a good idea.
Subway?
That's too exaggerated, too exaggerated
too exaggerated
Doraemon's word, can you make it?
Thinking of daddy taking
so crowded bus everyday
Really want daddy
go to work casually.
Doraemon
You are great,
your word is very nice to hear.
However, I only have digging machine.
Very good, try that then.
Start digging from here.
Keep this kind of thing
absolutely secret.
The company is in that direction.
Turn on the engine for digging machine.
Start
The speed is slower than thought.
Dig and move forward
How many days
if dig to the company.
Can not calculate it
What's this?
We are in sea
Now we have to dig again
What's that? Strange creature.
How terrible...
You are damaging public
asset. Sorry
Really finish it
before daddy's birthday?
Count on me
Today dig with right map.
What, what
This area is really hard
You come down and have
a look at the machine. Okay?
It sounds digging the earth.
Impossible, nobody
else except us
Just a little bit away
from daddy's company.
But how about railway and bus?
If lighting a little bit.
Only a little left
come on.
Daddy, look forward to
tomorrow's birthday
Good night.
Had a good sleep
What's this?
Daddy, happy birthday
Nobita and Doraemon
Thank you...
What's this?
(Nobi's home~company
Subway special ticket)
Whatever you think
this is impossible to use
Its' time to take crowded
bus go to work.
Be careful on the way, daddy
Daddy... use that special ticket
Possible? Really useful?
When did you make it?
We'll start up soon, get on the bus.
Please take out your special ticket
Is this one okay?
Sure
Start up
I have to go mom.
Be careful on the way.
This is simply great
I can go to work by sleeping
just like dreaming
Preset what time arrival?
Nobi's home's Subway
Our Subway
Very good, very good...
There is light ahead.
Emergency break
You can't run bus on railway.
There will be real bus coming through
But we dig here first
You can be so selfish
It's important to
serve the public, right?
Right
But it's not easy for daddy...
No other choice, we have
to dig else where.
From now on?
I am confused with directions
The machines stops.
What to do, What to do
Doraemon, any other choice?
Nothing
Do you really mean
I have to dig to the company?
That's impossible however you think.
Daddy, sorry. It's my
false to do so much
Sorry
Don't cry. You did that
thinking of daddy.
Only this daddy is already very happy.
It's light.
Concentrate digging here.
Dig out
Inside the hole
Anyway, get out of here.
Wonderful!
Great success, great success
What's the matter?
It's in front of the company
although spent some minutes.
But arrived a couple
of minutes before work.
Good that I am not late.
I have to work now.
Early go and early back
One time exam at least in the life.
Now I give you
the questions of yesterday.
Nobita
Yes.
As usual, only scores count.
Why are you so clever?
Everybody has to learn from you.
Admirable
I can't take it
Why no scores more than that?
He is the legendary talent
young man? How great.
Nobita is really great.
It's okay, nothing special.
Have you done your homework?
It's bad
What have you done since getting up?
Go to Shizuka's home?
As agreed for discussion in school
Everybody is waiting for you.
Don't you feel ashamed?
Can you finish your homework faster?
You talk too much.
Spend so much time
not even finish it? Sorry
I am slow anyway
Doraemon you go ahead.
Why become angry?
No solution for you
What's this?
Write your homework with that.
So great.
Finished
What's this?
Computer pencil
Let's go to Shizuka's home.
Give that to me back
Just lend that to me again.
Really interesting.
Give that back to me.
Are you still there?
Go to school discussion.
Today's homework is very
difficult and too much.
I haven't finished that until now.
I help you write it.
When do you become so clever?
To be honest homework not done yet
Give it here
Very strange
how does that idiot become talent?
There must be inside story.
We attend the school discussion
But...
My daddy works at home.
No disturb with noise
Nobita
Nobita, no disturb
That idiot.
He thinks he could
do adult work.
Sorry for disturbing.
How come so impolite?
Okay, all done.
What's the matter with you?
Indeed idiot can be dealt with medicine.
What do you say? Too impolite.
This is the result of daily hard work.
While you are sleeping well
I have to work very hard.
So, don't be sad.
Hi, Nobita
Give that back to me.
You played enough
Give that computer pencil back to me.
Nobita, give that back to me.
Lend it to me again
I have exams tomorrow.
Too sly. That's
considered to be cheating.
Ledn that to me.
Give that back to me.
It does not matter
That's cheating.
So is it, So is it
Thanks to that pencil.
Well, I want that, too.
Take it by all means
if you want anything.
I will take you around
the world during summer vacation.
Really?
I will buy everything
as long as you like.
Wonderful
Good night.
How can you promise
him everything, hubby?
I mean his scores
if he gets all in A.
That's impossible.
Don't; scare me.
Along 812.1% "m.
Doraemon, will also bring you there.
I don't want to use
mean way to travel the world.
Doraemon
Sly Nobita
His eyes look me down.
A pair of ugly eye$_
I don't care
I have to use it tomorrow.
Everybody gets the questions?
Yes.
Now start.
Doraemon
Leave it. Use common pencil.
You get it back. I did not use
that during today's exam.
Very great
Maybe you get a zero.
That's not.
What is not?
You look at it carefully.
This is a fake
made of usual pencil.
Very strange
Where was that replaced?
This exam was quit tough
Nobody gets a good mark.
Except one.
Gian, really worked hard.
That means
Give that computer pencil back to me.
I don't understand what you are talking
Give that back to me, Gian
painful
Daddy, look
it's score
Happy to tears.
How can you get any score
if you got nothing usually?
I should have taught you
Forget about the natural idiot.
But never cheat
These damned things even given to you.
What's the matter with you?
I don't want any score.
asia_cartoons@sinaman.com
Game of exchanging mom.
Why don't you listen to your mom?
Such a bad kid
is not our kid
Get out of here
regardless where do you go.
Don't; be sad
That's not really from heart.
But so what?
It's too much to say that.
That's true
NO need so angry.
That's right. YOU don't
understand kid's heart.
Yes
Newly become parent.
What's that? What's that?
Suneo and Shizuka
are both criticized by mom.
I also have something to say.
Of course I have.
My mom did not care
about me very early.
Whatever mom is not matching
my devil mom at home.
No, my mom is really fierce.
It's my mom.
No, it's my mom.
Absolutely, it's my mom.
It's my mom for sure.
No, It's my mom.
Okay, everybody, don't; be so sad.
We'd better exchange mom
temporarily, how about that?
First align your pictures well.
Then get ready
with your mom's picture.
Shuffle the cards carefully.
Nobita is Shizuka's mom
Shizuka is Suneo's mom
Suneo is Nobita's mom
Shared ready?
How about that? satisfied?
No problem, as long
as mom can be exchanged.
Family combination
Put these pair of pictures
into that family combination
Put it into.
So it's good.
Everybody goes to his
her new mom.
Shizuka's home is here.
It does not matter.
Her mom has become
your mom. Get in.
Get in...
Say I am back
Painful
Embarrassing
What are you talking about?
I even said it does not matter.
Hurry, get in...
Not good.
Hurry...
What are you doing?
Sorry for disturbing.
Nobita, what's the matter with you?
Is that your own home?
I lam back
Back? Cake is
on the shelf.
Wash your hands before eating.
Okay
What a gentle mom
Nobita said was too exaggerated.
Nobita
Yes
Please excuse mom
about the matter before.
What's the matter?
I just criticized you before
regarding the piano.
No It does not matter
Because it wasn't me
Very good mom
Shizuka really does not know enough.
Shizuka, this is your change.
Thank you
Hopefully you will not dislike
mom because of that matter.
Suneo even said devil mom
That's too extreme.
All of them are playing dolls.
Girl's room
nothing others.
No single piece I can play.
Sometimes I come and help.
Clean it with more power...
Look
If everyday like that
nobody will criticize you.
Maybe
Nobita is really a good kid
Nothing worth to mention
Every time you are like that
if somebody praises you.
Clean your body and take this on.
Thank you, mom
How come we have
girl's cloths at home?
Shizuka, such a good mom
you even call her devil mom
This is really too much.
Suneo's mom is also very gentle.
Nobita should condemn herself.
Mom is eventually also common people.
Occasionally they become angry
because of misunderstanding.
Maybe angry with
somebody, quite usual
Mom is not god
Right
Then we won't exchange mom any more.
But really changed back?
Don't worry, pictures taken
out from family combination.
We are back.
Not even changed back at all, look.
What's the matter actually?Even forgot
underwear at Shizuka's home.
It bothered you all bringing it back.
That's right
Air combat
Too noisy!
Dead with you, dead with you...
What's this?
Mini plane
It's made simply
like a real one.
Also borrow you one
How to get on?
Soon as you get on
your body will become small.
How to drive?
You look besides your feet.
Right foot forward
left food backward.
The grip in the middle
push is for rising
Pull is for landing.
Turn right is right
Turn left is left
You try to fly.
It really can move.
You want to hit the desk.
Push the grip.
Very good, very good.
Its' very simple when getting used to.
Damned
Be polite.
Give that model back to me.
Never
Gian is abusing others again.
Come and get it if you can
Give that back to me.
What's that?
Your model is great.
I have other. Then borrow to you.
Unforgivable
Mine is okay now.
I like this one
No problem
I want this one.
Well, you mistaken, that's mine.
Only this old one left
Hi, wait a moment.
See how I take revenge against you.
That guy, Gian
Where were you?
Around and behind me.
Lost the war.
Everybody loses it
Very funny.
It's Tokyo Tower
Have a break there.
Beautiful sight
This is not sight view
place but real tower top.
Very comfortable
On top of Tokyo Tower
a crying boy is found.
A helicopter is sent
causing a lot of unrest.
asia_cartoon@hotmail.com
Door out of nothing.
No
I I want to keep my mind.
You are often saving money recently
I want to be independent
thus have to save money.
Independent?
I want to try
my own capability.
Why do you say that?
In my daily life
Everything has to
rely on daddy and mom
I feel ashamed because of incapability
Therefore, encouraged to
move out and rent a room
Test my own ability
but
It's hard to save money.
Great
painful...
Normally you are spoilt
no courage and brain
Now even become so determined
Let me give you a hand.
Do you want to rent me a room?
I don't have so much money
But can make you independent.
If here, you don't
need to pay me money but live here.
Really?
The landlord here doesn't have
any house number just for good luck
Beside room number
immediately room number
Then
Paste the door out of
nothing onto the wall with nothing
New room will appear
Inside it's the same like other rooms.
Then just dismantle the door everything
outside will be back to normal.
Turn back to a wall
Is this your private secret room?
Simply great
I want to live in this room
very bravely further.
Okay
Get away from home
ls your mom worried about you?
No, it would be better
if she worries.
Then mom would understand
how important I am her single son.
I am free and independent
Wonderful
Really happy
I can do whatever I want to.
That's not your goal
to do whatever you want.
Who are you?
Who is the nanny?
Those living in rooms
Here you have room number.
I am really too careless.
You have to dismantle the door.
If found you have
to pay the rent
ls there any room number?
I don't know whether mom
has found me left home.
If knew that before, we'll condemned him
Or give him more change
Don't know whether thought of that.
I don't' know.
But all students will admire my
Great courage and practice.
I do not know.
Shizuka, come and play with me.
I rent a room and you
can also come with others.
She does not believe
I think so.
Somebody is talking outside.
Seemingly coming
Load it on
I told you all. There is no
more room number here.
But in telephone
they do say there is room number.
I am the landlord
of this apartment building
If I say no, there is no more.
What room number? Not lucky
Go back, go back.
I do feel strange.
He likes big mouth.
Next time when I see him
I will beat him heavily.
Call them from this side.
Hi, wait.
Shizuka
Gian, wait
Mom
Run
Run, fast
That kid runs away as soon
he sees me. How come?
Please, does it work
if you do nothing like that?
Lots of homework to be done.
Although I know it won't
work if not write them
But I get used to be
criticized by mom and then write them.
No criticize, not homework, right?
What's the matter?
I think of that.
Which one?
It's Nobita
You can't just play around
go and do the homework.
Nobita, where do you go?
Come back for homework.
Finally starts writing
Nobita, I have to be back.
Ordered cake is coming.
I seem to be hungry.
If eaten up all the breds
brought here
We have to make food
for us own. That would be a problem.
Very hot...
Hot, hot
You have to wash your own cloths
Hi, turn down the volume of your radio.
What's this?
Disturbed your family.
That's right. Our kids
can't sleep.
Very sorry, we
don't have any radio.
Noisy apartment
Mom has not realized
I let home.
Or is looking for me now.
But if I am here, it would
be very difficult to find me.
Right, you'd better move to
where your mom can easily find you.
Really very busy
Bus'!
Mom has even not realized my leaving.
Its' terrible for kids
having this kind of parents.
Hm, always feel right.
Become independent
it seems too early.
Somebody's face is round
Somebody's face is long
Somebody's face is square
Somebody's face is triangle
If cry, become angry
play temper
Crying one will become an devil.
But be happy and laugh.
Everybody's face is actually round.